Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Office of the Chancellor Records, 1933-2014
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1933-2011, UWM Archival Collection 46; 220.4 cubic ft. (224 boxes) 2 film reels 718 digital files (539 MB)
  - 6. Zimpher Administration Records, 1991-2011
    - Subject Files, 1991-2011
      - Framework for Technology, 1999 (Box 191, Folder 19)
      - French and Italian, Department of, 1998-2002 (Box 182, Folder 50)
      - Freshman Scholars, 2002 (Box 182, Folder 51)
      - From the Heart Lecture Series, 1998 (Box 182, Folder 52)
      - Fromkin, Morris, Lecture Series, 1998-2000 (Box 182, Folder 53)
      - Fulbright Scholar Program, 1998-2001 (Box 182, Folder 54)
      - Fundraising, 1998-2002 (Box 182, Folder 55)
      - Gates Foundation, 2003 (Box 224, Folder 2)
      - Gates Proposal, 2003 (Box 224, Folder 3)
      - Gay and Lesbian Issues, 1999-2003 (Box 182, Folder 56)
      - Gear Up
        - 1999-2000 (Box 191, Folder 20)
        - 2000-2001 (Box 182, Folder 57)
      - General Electric, 2000 (Box 182, Folder 58)
      - Geography, Department of, 1998-2000 (Box 182, Folder 59)
      - Geosciences, Department of, 1999-2001 (Box 182, Folder 60)
      - Global Studies, 2002 (Box 182, Folder 61)
      - Global University Alliance, 2000-2003 (Box 182, Folder 62)
      - Golden Key Honor Society, 1998-2000 (Box 182, Folder 63)
      - Governor, State of Wisconsin, 1998-2001 (Box 182, Folder 64)
      - Governor's Trade Missions, 1998-2003 (Box 182, Folder 65)
      - Graduate School (Box 183, Folder 1)
        - 1998-2003 (Box 183, Folder 1)
        - 2000-2011 (Box 191, Folder 21-22)
        - UWM Foundation Research Awards, 1998-2001 (Box 183, Folder 2)
      - Graduation Rates, 2000 (Box 183, Folder 3)
      - Grand Avenue Center, 2001 (Box 183, Folder 4)
      - Grants: Summary of Objectives, 1999-2003 (Box 191, Folder 23)
      - Great Books Program, 2000 (Box 183, Folder 5)
      - Great Lakes Research Facility, 1998-1999 (Box 183, Folder 6)
      - Great Lakes WATER Institute, 1998-2002 (Box 183, Folder 7)
      - Greater Milwaukee Committee, 1997-2003 (Box 183, Folder 8)
      - Greater Milwaukee Convention and Visitors Bureau, 1999-2002 (Box 183, Folder 9)
      - Greater Milwaukee Education Trust, 1998 (Box 183, Folder 10)
      - Greater Milwaukee Foundation, 1998-2003 (Box 183, Folder 11)
      - Greater Milwaukee Nonprofit Institute, 2001 (Box 183, Folder 12)
      - Greene Museum, 2001 (Box 183, Folder 13)
      - Guild for Learning in Retirement, 1999-2003 (Box 183, Folder 14)
      - Guskin, Al, 1999 (Box 183, Folder 15)
      - Harley Davidson, 1999-2002 (Box 183, Folder 16)
      - Hartford Avenue School, 1992-1999 (Box 183, Folder 17)
      - Harvard Club, 2003 (Box 183, Folder 18)
      - Health Care, 1999-2003 (Box 183, Folder 19)
      - Health Sciences, College of, 1998-2003 (Box 183, Folder 20)
      - Hebrew University of Jerusalem, 2003 (Box 183, Folder 21)
      - Hefty, Thomas, 1999-2000 (Box 183, Folder 22)
      - Higher Education Act, 2003 (Box 183, Folder 23)
      - Higher Education Aids Board, 1998 (Box 183, Folder 24)
      - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce, 1999-2003 (Box 183, Folder 25)
      - History, Department of, 1998-2002 (Box 183, Folder 26)
      - History PhD, 2000-2003 (Box 183, Folder 27)
      - Homecoming, 2001-2003 (Box 183, Folder 28)
      - Honorary Degrees, 1995-2003 (Box 183, Folder 29)
      - Honorary Sciences, 1999 (Box 183, Folder 30)
      - Honors Convocation, Senior and Sophomore, 1998-2003 (Box 183, Folder 31)
      - Honors Initiatives, 2000 (Box 183, Folder 32)
      - Honors Program, 1998-2001 (Box 183, Folder 33)
      - Horizon League, 1999-2003 (Box 183, Folder 34)
      - Human Kinetics, 1999-2001 (Box 183, Folder 35)
      - Human Resources Reports and Correspondence, 1998-2010 (Box 191, Folder 24)
      - IBM Proposal for Technology, 1999 (Box 183, Folder 36)
      - Impact, 2000 (Box 183, Folder 37)
      - Improving Teacher Quality, 1999 (Box 220, Folder 2)
      - Inaugural Address, 1999 (Box 183, Folder 38)
      - Inauguration Invitations, 1999-2003 (Box 183, Folder 39)
      - Independence First, 2003 (Box 183, Folder 40)
      - Indian Community School
        - 1998-2001 (Box 183, Folder 41)
        - 1999-2006 (Box 191, Folder 25)
      - Information and Media Technology, 1998-2002 (Box 183, Folder 42)
      - Information Studies, School of, 1998-2003 (Box 183, Folder 43)
      - Institute for Chamber Music, 1999 (Box 183, Folder 44)
      - Institute for Global Studies, 1999-2000 (Box 183, Folder 45)
      - Institute of Visual Arts, 1998-2002 (Box 183, Folder 47)
      - Institute of World Affairs, 1998-2003 (Box 183, Folder 48)
      - Institute on Race and Ethnicity, 1999-2000 (Box 183, Folder 46)
      - Institutional Competition Review, 1999-2003 (Box 183, Folder 49)
      - Instruction and Professional Development, Center for, 1999-2003 (Box 183, Folder 50)
      - Instructional and Research Academic Survey, 2001-2002 (Box 183, Folder 51)
      - Interagency Education Research Initiative (IERI) Grant, 2003 (Box 224, Folder 4)
      - Interinstitutional Agreements, 1993-2001 (Box 183, Folder 52)
      - Internal Audit, 1999-2002 (Box 183, Folder 53)
      - International Arts Festival, 2000 (Box 183, Folder 54)
      - International DIN, 1998-1999 (Box 183, Folder 55)
      - International Education, Center for, 1998-2003 (Box 183, Folder 56)
      - International Institute of Wisconsin's World Citizen Award, 2000 (Box 183, Folder 57)
      - International Women's Forum, 1998-2001 (Box 183, Folder 58)
      - Investing in Wisconsin's Future, 2000 (Box 191, Folder 26)
      - Irish Festival, 1999 (Box 183, Folder 59)
      - Israel Cultural Mission, 1999-2002 (Box 183, Folder 60)
      - Jane Bradley Petitt Foundation, 2002 (Box 183, Folder 61)
      - Jewish Learning, 1997-1998 (Box 191, Folder 27)
      - Jewish Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 183, Folder 62)
      - Job Corps Center, 2002-2003 (Box 183, Folder 63)
      - Johnson Foundation, Johnson Wax Professional, 2000-2002 (Box 183, Folder 64)
      - Joint Finance Committee, 1999-2001 (Box 183, Folder 65)
      - Joint Venture
        - 2001 (Box 183, Folder 66)
        - 2002 (Box 191, Folder 28)
        - Steering Committee, 2001 (Box 191, Folder 29)
      - Jones Island, 1999 (Box 183, Folder 67)
      - Journalism and Mass Communication, Department of, 1998-2003 (Box 183, Folder 68)
      - Junior Achievement, 2002 (Box 183, Folder 69)
      - Kahler Slater, 1998-1999 (Box 183, Folder 70)
      - Keimyung University, 1998 (Box 183, Folder 71)
      - Kikkoman, 2003 (Box 183, Folder 72)
      - Klotsche Center
        - 1999-2001 (Box 183, Folder 73)
        - Environmental Impact Statement, Draft, 2001 (Box 183, Folder 74)
      - Klotsche Family, 1999-2001 (Box 183, Folder 75)
      - Korean Film Festival, 2001 (Box 183, Folder 76)
      - Kuttemperoor, Vincent, VK Development Corporation, 1999-2000 (Box 183, Folder 77)
      - Labor Unions, 1998-2003 (Box 183, Folder 78)
      - LaCausa, 1999-2003 (Box 183, Folder 79)
      - Lapham Hall, 1998-1999 (Box 183, Folder 80)
      - Late Night Events, 1998 (Box 183, Folder 81)
      - Latino Community, 1998 (Box 191, Folder 30)
      - Latino Student Union, 1999 (Box 183, Folder 82)
      - Latino/Hispanic Advisory Committee and Hispanic Issues, 1990-2001 (Box 183, Folder 83)
      - Leader [Student Newspaper], 2001-2002 (Box 183, Folder 84)
      - Leadership and Leaders Forum, 1999-2003 (Box 183, Folder 85)
      - Learning Technology Center, 1999 (Box 183, Folder 86)
      - Lectures Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 183, Folder 87)
      - Legal Affairs
        - 1999-2001 (Box 183, Folder 88)
        - Review, 1999 (Box 191, Folder 31)
      - Legislative Correspondence, 1998-2003 (Box 183, Folder 89-90)
      - Letters and Science, College of, 1998-2002 (Box 184, Folder 1)
      - Library, Golda Meir, 1998-2003 (Box 184, Folder 2)
      - Lighthouse Project, 1999 (Box 184, Folder 3)
      - Logo
        - 1999-2000 (Box 184, Folder 4)
        - 2001 (Box 191, Folder 32)
      - Lynch, Richard (Dick) L., 2001-2003 (Box 192, Folder 1)
      - Manpower, Elmer Winter, 1999-2003 (Box 184, Folder 5)
      - Marcus Corporation, 2000-2002 (Box 184, Folder 6)
      - Marketing Plan, 1996 (Box 192, Folder 2)
      - Marquette University, 2000-2001 (Box 184, Folder 7)
      - Materials Department, 1998 (Box 192, Folder 3)
      - Math and Science Education, 1999-2002 (Box 184, Folder 8)
      - Mathematical Sciences, Department of, 1999-2002 (Box 184, Folder 9)
      - Mayor's Office, 1999-2003 (Box 184, Folder 10)
      - Medical College of Wisconsin, 1998-2002 (Box 184, Folder 11)
      - Menomonee Valley Initiative, 2003 (Box 192, Folder 4)
      - Metropolitan Milwaukee Association of Commerce, 1997-2003 (Box 184, Folder 12)
      - Metropolitan Multicultural Teacher Education Program (MMTEP), 1997 (Box 192, Folder 5)
      - Miller Brewing Company, 2000 (Box 184, Folder 13)
      - Milwaukee Area Technical College (MATC)
        - 1999-2003 (Box 184, Folder 14)
        - 2000 (Box 192, Folder 6)
      - Milwaukee Art Museum, 1999-2002 (Box 184, Folder 15)
      - Milwaukee Awards for Neighborhood Development Innovation, 1999 (Box 184, Folder 16)
      - Milwaukee Brewers, 2001-2003 (Box 184, Folder 17)
      - Milwaukee Business Forum, 1999-2003 (Box 184, Folder 18)
      - Milwaukee Center for Independence, 2001-2003 (Box 184, Folder 19)
      - Milwaukee Center for Workplace Diversity, 2002-2004 (Box 184, Folder 20)
      - Milwaukee College Life, 2001-2002 (Box 184, Folder 22)
      - Milwaukee Commitment
        - 1998-2003 (Box 184, Folder 23)
        - 1999 (Box 192, Folder 7)
      - Milwaukee Ethnic Council, 1998-2003 (Box 184, Folder 25)
      - Milwaukee Graduate Assistants Association, 1999-2003 (Box 184, Folder 26)
      - Milwaukee Idea
        - 1999-2003 (Box 184, Folder 27)
        - 1999-2003 (Box 220, Folder 3-4)
        - Brochures, undated (Box 184, Folder 28)
        - Bulletin, 2000-2002 (Box 184, Folder 29)
        - Home Event, 2003 (Box 220, Folder 5)
        - Launch, 2003-2004 (Box 220, Folder 6)
        - Presentation, 1999 (Box 192, Folder 8)
        - Quick Wins, 2003 (Box 220, Folder 7)
        - Taking Stock, 2001 (Box 220, Folder 8)
      - Milwaukee Initiative, 2000 (Box 220, Folder 9)
      - Milwaukee Inner City Congregations Allied for Hope (MICAH), 2000 (Box 184, Folder 30)
      - Milwaukee International Health Training Center, 2001-2002 (Box 184, Folder 31)
      - Milwaukee Jewish Council/Federation, 1998-2003 (Box 184, Folder 32)
      - Milwaukee Magazine, 1999-2000 (Box 184, Folder 33)
      - Milwaukee Partnership Academy
        - American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education, 2000
        - Board Meeting Minutes, 2001-2003 (Box 224, Folder 5-22)
        - Board Retreat, 2001-2002 (Box 224, Folder 23-24)
        - Call to Action, 2002 (Box 224, Folder 25-27)
        - Care Packages, 2002 (Box 192, Folder 9)
        - Consortium Agreement, 2002 (Box 224, Folder 28)
        - Correspondence and Miscellaneous, 2000-2004 (Box 192, Folder 10-13)
        - Executive Committee, 2002
        - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 2002-2004 (Box 224, Folder 29-34)
        - Executive Director, 2002-2004 (Box 224, Folder 35)
        - Implementation Meetings, 2001-2003 (Box 192, Folder 14-16)
        - Implementation Team Reports, 2002 (Box 192, Folder 17-18)
        - Literacy Framework, 2001-2003 (Box 192, Folder 19)
        - Media Coverage, 2000-2002 (Box 192, Folder 20)
        - Meeting, Agenda, and Minutes, 2000 (Box 192, Folder 21-23)
        - Meeting Files, 2000-2002
        - Mission Statement, 2000-2001 (Box 192, Folder 24)
        - Multiple Pathways to Teaching, 2001 (Box 192, Folder 25)
        - National Science Foundation (NSF) Grant Proposal, 2002-2003 (Box 192, Folder 26)
        - Partnership for Education, 2002 (Box 192, Folder 27)
        - Press, 2002 (Box 192, Folder 28)
        - Program of Distinction Award, 2003 (Box 224, Folder 36)
        - Retreat, 2000 (Box 192, Folder 29)
        - Staff, 2002 (Box 224, Folder 37)
        - Website, 2000 (Box 192, Folder 30)
        - Workshop, 2001
        - Workshop, 2001 (Box 224, Folder 38)
        - Year 2 Work Plan and Budget, 2001 (Box 192, Folder 31)
        - Year 3 Work Plan, 2002 (Box 192, Folder 32)
        - Year 4 and Performance Review, 2003 (Box 192, Folder 33)
      - Milwaukee Public Library, 1998-2003 (Box 184, Folder 34)
      - Milwaukee Public Schools
        - 1998-2003 (Box 184, Folder 35)
        - Grant "PT3" (Preparing Tomorrow's Teachers for Technology), 2000-2001 (Box 193, Folder 1)
        - Powerpoint, 2001
      - Milwaukee School of Engineering, 1998-1999 (Box 184, Folder 36)
      - Milwaukee Teacher Education Center
        - 1999-2000 (Box 184, Folder 37)
        - 1999-2003 (Box 193, Folder 2)
      - Milwaukee Teachers Association, 2001 (Box 184, Folder 38)
      - Milwaukee Women's Center, 1999-2000 (Box 184, Folder 39)
      - Milwaukee, City of, 1998-2003 (Box 184, Folder 21)
      - Milwaukee, County of, 1999-2002 (Box 184, Folder 24)
      - Minority Business Program, 2000 (Box 184, Folder 38)
      - Minority Disadvantaged Programs, 1999 (Box 184, Folder 41)
      - Mission Statement, 1998-2001 (Box 184, Folder 42)
      - Mitchell International Airport, 2001 (Box 184, Folder 43)
      - Mortar Board, 1998 (Box 184, Folder 44)
      - Mount Mary College, 1998-1999 (Box 184, Folder 45)
      - Mueller Communications Inc., 2000-2002 (Box 184, Folder 46)
      - Multicultural Affairs, 1999-2003 (Box 184, Folder 47)
      - Music, Department of, 1998-2003 (Box 184, Folder 48)
      - National Alliance of Business, 1998-2002 (Box 184, Folder 49)
      - National Association for Advancement of Colored People, 1998-1999 (Box 184, Folder 50)
      - National Association of Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC), 2000-2003 (Box 184, Folder 51)
      - National Black United Front, 2000 (Box 184, Folder 52)
      - National Board for Professional Teaching, 1999-2003 (Box 184, Folder 53)
      - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA) (Box 184, Folder 54)
        - 1998-2003 (Box 184, Folder 55)
        - Self-Study Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 184, Folder 56)
      - National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education (NCATE), 2002 (Box 184, Folder 57)
      - National Science Foundation, 1998-2003 (Box 184, Folder 58)
      - Nativity Jesuit School, 1999 (Box 184, Folder 59)
      - Neighborhood Issues, 1999-2003 (Box 184, Folder 60)
      - Next Door Foundation, 2002 (Box 184, Folder 61)
      - Non-Resident Tuition, 1999 (Box 184, Folder 62)
      - Norris Health Center, 1998-2002 (Box 184, Folder 63)
      - North Carolina Partnership for Excellence, 1998-2002 (Box 184, Folder 64)
      - North Central Association of Colleges and Schools
        - 1998-2003 (Box 184, Folder 65)
        - 2005 Accrediation, 1995-2009 (Box 193, Folder 3-4)
      - Northeast Normal University, 2000 (Box 184, Folder 66)
      - Northwest Side Community Development, 1999 (Box 184, Folder 67)
      - Northwestern Mutual, 1999-2002 (Box 184, Folder 68)
      - Notebaert Chair, 1999-2001 (Box 184, Folder 69)
      - Nursing, School of, 1998-2003 (Box 184, Folder 70)
      - Online Access Student Information System (OASIS), 1998-2001 (Box 184, Folder 71)
      - Open House, 1998-2003 (Box 184, Folder 72)
      - Outside Activities, 1998-2003 (Box 184, Folder 73)
      - Overseas Academic Programming, 1998-2000 (Box 184, Folder 74)
      - Pabst Theater, 2001 (Box 184, Folder 75)
      - Panther Sports and Rental, 1999 (Box 184, Folder 76)
      - Parking and Transit, 1996-2003 (Box 184, Folder 77)
      - Partners Advancing Values in Education, 1999 (Box 184, Folder 78)
      - Partnerships, 1998 (Box 193, Folder 5)
      - Partnerships and Innovation, 2000-2001 (Box 184, Folder 79)
      - Partnerships for Environmental Health Action Team, 1999-2003 (Box 184, Folder 80)
      - Peace Corps, 2002 (Box 184, Folder 81)
      - Peace Studies, 1998-2000 (Box 184, Folder 82)
      - Peck School of the Arts, 1998-2003 (Box 184, Folder 83)
      - Peoplesoft, 1998-1999 (Box 193, Folder 6)
      - Phi Beta Kappa, Phi Delta Kappa, Phi Eta Sigma, Phi Kappa Phi, Pi Lambda, 1998-2003 (Box 184, Folder 84)
      - Philosophy, Department of, 1999-2001 (Box 184, Folder 85)
      - Physical Environment Committee, 1998-2003 (Box 184, Folder 86)
      - Physical Plant Services, 1997-2002 (Box 184, Folder 87)
      - Physics, Department of, 1999-2003 (Box 184, Folder 88)
      - Pier Wisconsin, 2001-2003 (Box 185, Folder 1)
      - Plan 2008, 1998-2003 (Box 185, Folder 2)
      - Plenary
        - 1999
        - 2002 (Box 185, Folder 3)
      - Police, 1998-2003 (Box 185, Folder 4)
      - Political Science, Department of, 1998-2003 (Box 185, Folder 5)
      - Population Health, Center for, 2000 (Box 185, Folder 6)
      - Potawatomi, 2001-2003 (Box 185, Folder 7)
      - Pre-College Academy, 1998-2001 (Box 185, Folder 8)
      - Preparations and Planning Report, 1999 (Box 193, Folder 7)
      - Presentation to Public Policy Forum, "What Works in Urban Schools," 2003 (Box 193, Folder 8)
      - President Bush Visit, 2002 (Box 185, Folder 9)
      - Private Industry Council, 1999-2002 (Box 185, Folder 10)
      - Professional Theatre Training Program, 1999-2001 (Box 185, Folder 11)
      - Program Array Review, 1998-2000 (Box 185, Folder 12)
      - Project Equality, 1999 (Box 185, Folder 13)
      - Prospective Partners, 2000 (Box 193, Folder 9)
      - Psychology, Department of, 1999-2003 (Box 185, Folder 14)
      - Public Administration Joint Degree, 2002 (Box 185, Folder 15)
      - Public Policy Forum, 1998-2001 (Box 185, Folder 16)
      - Quality Education Commission, 1998 (Box 185, Folder 17)
      - Quebec Trade Mission, 2000 (Box 185, Folder 18)
      - Racioethnicity Task Force Leadership Team, 2003 (Box 185, Folder 19)
      - Recruitment and Retention, 1995-2001 (Box 185, Folder 20)
      - Regents, Board of, 1998-2003 (Box 185, Folder 23)
      - Regional Economic Strategy, 2001
      - Report to the Community, 2002 (Box 185, Folder 21)
      - Report to the Regents, 2000 (Box 185, Folder 22)
      - Regional Economic Partnerships, 1999 (Box 185, Folder 24)
      - Research Plan, 1998-1999 (Box 185, Folder 25)
      - Research Profile, 2001 (Box 185, Folder 26)
      - Rethinking Schools, 1999 (Box 185, Folder 27)
      - Retired Faculty Association, 1998-2002 (Box 185, Folder 28)
      - Revere Group, 1999-2000 (Box 185, Folder 29)
      - Riverside High School
        - 1999-2000 (Box 185, Folder 30)
        - 2003 (Box 193, Folder 10)
      - Roberto Hernandez Center
        - 1998-2002 (Box 185, Folder 31)
        - 2000-2005 (Box 193, Folder 11)
      - Rockwell Automation, 2001 (Box 185, Folder 32)
      - Salaries, 1998-2000 (Box 185, Folder 33)
      - Salary Adjustment Guidelines, 1998-1999 (Box 185, Folder 34)
      - Sandburg Residence Halls, 1999-2003 (Box 185, Folder 35)
      - SBC Communications Inc., Ameritech, 1998-2002 (Box 185, Folder 36)
      - Scholarships, 1998-2002 (Box 185, Folder 37)
      - Schooler, Dean, 1998-1999 (Box 185, Folder 38)
      - Schooner, 1999-2001 (Box 185, Folder 39)
      - Schultz, Lester, 1998-2003 (Box 185, Folder 40)
      - Science Bag, 1999-2002 (Box 185, Folder 41)
      - Scouts, Girl and Boy, 1998-2002 (Box 185, Folder 42)
      - Search and Screen
        - Development, 2001-2003 (Box 185, Folder 43)
        - General, 1998-1999 (Box 185, Folder 44)
        - University Relations, 1999-2002 (Box 185, Folder 45)
      - Secretary of the University, 1998-2001 (Box 185, Folder 46)
      - Secretary's Summit on Teacher Equality, 1999 (Box 185, Folder 47)
      - Self-Study Report, 1992 (Box 193, Folder 12)
      - Service Learning
        - 1998 (Box 193, Folder 13)
        - 1998-2003 (Box 185, Folder 48)
      - Shaw Scientists Program, 1999 (Box 185, Folder 49)
      - Sick Leave Policy, 1998 (Box 185, Folder 50)
      - Social Development Commission, 2000-2003 (Box 185, Folder 51)
      - Social Welfare, Helen Bader School of, 1998-2003 (Box 185, Folder 52)
      - Sociology, Department of, 1998-2002 (Box 185, Folder 53)
      - Southeast Wisconsin Regional Planning Committee, 2000 (Box 193, Folder 14-16)
      - Southeast Wisconsin White Paper, 2000 (Box 193, Folder 17)
      - Southeastern Wisconsin Regional Paper, 2001
      - Southern at 150 Correspondence, 2003 (Box 193, Folder 18)
      - Spaights Plaza Nominees, 1998-2003 (Box 185, Folder 54)
      - Spanish & Portuguese, Department of, 1998-2001 (Box 185, Folder 55)
      - Speeches
        - 1998 (Box 193, Folder 19)
        - 2003
      - Spirit of Milwaukee, 1999-2002 (Box 185, Folder 56)
      - Start Smart Milwaukee, 1999 (Box 185, Folder 57)
      - State Employees Combined Campaign (SECC), 1998-2002 (Box 185, Folder 58)
      - State Higher Education Executive Officers (SHEEO), 1999-2000 (Box 185, Folder 59)
      - Sterry, Len, 1999-2001 (Box 193, Folder 20)
      - Strategic Alliance, Strategic Plan, 1998-2000 (Box 185, Folder 60)
      - Student Achievement Guarantee in Education (SAGE), 2000-2001 (Box 185, Folder 61)
      - Student Affairs, 1998-2003 (Box 185, Folder 62)
      - Student Association, 1999-2001 (Box 185, Folder 63)
      - Student Correspondence, 1998-2003 (Box 185, Folder 64)
      - Student Information System, 1999 (Box 185, Folder 65)
      - Student Life, 1998 (Box 185, Folder 66)
      - Student Organizations, 1999-2001 (Box 185, Folder 67)
      - Student Technology Fee, 1998-2000 (Box 185, Folder 68)
      - Sullivan/Spaights Professorship
        - 1998-2002 (Box 185, Folder 69)
        - 2001-2004 (Box 193, Folder 21)
      - Systems, Applications, and Products, 1998-1999 (Box 185, Folder 70)
      - Talent Search, 1997-2001 (Box 185, Folder 72)
      - Task Force on Race and Ethnicity, 2002 (Box 193, Folder 22)
      - Task Force on the Status of Women, 2000-2001 (Box 186, Folder 71)
      - Teacher-In-Residence, 2000 (Box 193, Folder 23)
      - Tech Grant, 1999-2003 (Box 193, Folder 24)
      - Tech On-Line, 2000 (Box 193, Folder 25)
      - TechStar
        - Board of Directors Meeting, 2003 (Box 193, Folder 26-27)
        - Boards: Milwaukee School of Engineering/Marquette/Medical College of Wisconsin, 2002 (Box 193, Folder 28)
        - Business Plan, 2000-2002 (Box 193, Folder 29-30)
        - Chancellors/Presidents Meeting, 2002 (Box 193, Folder 31)
        - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 193, Folder 32-36)
        - Executive Director and Other Positions, 2001 (Box 194, Folder 1)
        - Meeting Information, 2000-2001 (Box 194, Folder 2)
        - Miscellaneous Documents, 2001-2003 (Box 194, Folder 3-5)
        - Models, 2000-2001 (Box 194, Folder 6)
        - Notes & Miscellaneous, 2000-2001 (Box 194, Folder 7)
        - Press, 2000-2001 (Box 194, Folder 8)
        - University Technology Transfer (UTT) Activities, 2000 (Box 194, Folder 9)
      - Temple Emanu-El B'ne Jeshurun, 1998-2002 (Box 185, Folder 73)
      - Ten Chimneys Foundation, 2000-2003 (Box 185, Folder 74)
      - The Association of University of Wisconsin Professionals (TAUWP), 1998-2000 (Box 185, Folder 75)
      - Theater and Dance, 1997-2003 (Box 185, Folder 76)
      - Title II: Recruitment, 1999 (Box 194, Folder 10)
      - Title 6, 2003 (Box 185, Folder 77)
      - Trade Missions, 1999 (Box 185, Folder 78)
      - Tuition and Fees, 1999-2001 (Box 185, Folder 79)
      - Tutoring, 1999-2003 (Box 185, Folder 80)
      - Twentieth and Twenty-First Century Studies, Center for, 1998-2002 (Box 185, Folder 81)
      - Unclassified Pay Plan, 2003 (Box 194, Folder 11)
      - Union, 1999-2002 (Box 185, Folder 82)